Hello friends, welcome to a new video.
Actually, I have come to the
TVS service center with my Rohini and
I had to get a photograph of the Rohini clicked,
so my photo is ready.
[Sangeet]
Finally, my car is ready.
You must have seen that I had made a video of the accident.
This is my Rohini and
[Sangeet]
all the official work has been done, there are some other things
which have not come.
[Sangeet]
And my brother from Sarnath, who
lives here and used to be very small, has
grown a lot.
[Sangeet]
So, some changes have been made in him, so everything had to be
checked to see what needs to be done,
for that you can see the rest of the car.
We have been having it for a long time, I saw it today, which has been
quite some time, you can see the rest.
[Sangeet]
Bhaiya ji is quite busy, this is my brother
Diwakar bhaiya.
[Sangeet]
And I always get my bike repaired from him, I keep
talking about it whenever it happens,
friends, you can see this. I have
your
TVS riding jacket in my dream.
When I buy my super bike, I will try to get it for the office as well.
And I will tell you the whole thing about this
in the next video, the
rest of my bike has been reduced,
finally what about my bike and
my bike has been reduced, all the claims of the vehicle were passed,
all the clamps were passed and its tank was replaced
and there are many other things about it, if you
ask then I will make a separate video in it
and right now yours has not been reduced, this meter is still
lacking, the meter will be installed, the
meter is not there yet and there is one
thing about the green, the green is yet to be installed, there is a
problem with the rear stand, let's check that as well, the
rest you can see the road here,
this goes to your Pandeypur and the
guards here are your Mishra TVS, do
n't leave it brother, slowly
Mishra TVS is the agency where I bought my
first bike from here 12 years ago, since then
I have been buying bikes from here continuously till today
and this is my bike, actually it has been
photographed, I only had to take a photo
of the bike and my bike is ready and I will take
it home, so friends
how did you like this video, please tell me by commenting,
I will make such videos for you people because it is
important to make videos of bikes because of the
new series  I had a bike and I had
made a review video of it, then I had made an accident, then
I had made the video, the rest you
can see there is a lot to tell in this video,
now when it will be done, its front has
also been changed and the meter, so right now
I will show you the inside part of the meter, this is the
complete meter, not only is it its meter, it
also has a Bluetooth system, so there is another
meter, I mean the
meter of the top variant of the classic bike has been installed, the
rest of the bike is for my reading at home
and my bike is ready
[Music]